Killer Mountain is a adventure, tv movie, horror
film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
A team of  climbers is assembled by a rich and eccentric man to rescue a missing expedition he sent up to
a forbidden mountain who disappeared after sending out one last disturbing radio message.
Kate Donovan, played by Emmanuelle Vaugier.
Ward Donovan, played by Aaron Douglas.
Tyler, played by Paul Campbell.
Dr. Nina Preston, played by Yan-Kay Crystal Lowe.
Rogers, played by Curtis Caravaggio.
Chance, played by Torrance Coombs.
Killer Elite is a 2011 action thriller film directed by Gary McKendry and
starring Jason Statham, Clive Owen and Robert De Niro.
The film is based on the 1991 novel The Feather Men by Ranulph Fiennes.
The film marked the debut of Open Road Films.
It was released in the United States on 23 September 2011
and received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is dark.